When the input consists of N integers from 1 to 23, the complexity is (n!)^2.
For a n-digit sequence, if we randomly pick two numbers and consider adding, dividing, multiplying ,subtracting, divided and subtracted as six optional method, we have 6*n*(n-1)/2 (n-1) possibilities.
The corresponding operation time will be [6^(n-1)] * n*[(n-1)^2]*[(n-2)^2]*¡­¡­*1/[2^(n-1)]. Furthermore, the total operation time will be [3^(n-1)]*[(n!)^2]/n.
In conclusion, the estimated complexity is (n!)^2. It is not the most efficient choice but it works. 